Lawunn Khaing

IT student

Personal details

Name Lawunn Khaing

Email address lawunnkhaing.tgi@gmail.com

Phone number +358 417918422

Address Raviradantie 11, 50100 Mikkeli, Finland

Website lawunnkhaing.netlify.app

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/lawunn-khaing-8980441ab

Github github.com/LawunnKhaing



About Me

A highly motivated and enthusiastic IT student with a passion for technology and a strong foundation in programming and experienced in networking and security. I possess a positive attitude, excellent communication skills, and the ability to work well in a team.

Education

Aug 2022 - Present Bachelor of Engineering (Information Technology)

South-Eastern Finland University Of Applied Sciences, Finland

Dec 2018 - Mar 2020 Bachelor of Engineering (Computer Engineering)

Yangon Technological University, Myanmar

Work Experience

Mar 2016 - Dec 2016 Language Teacher

Buddhist Chinese Monastery, Myanmar

I used to teach the little

Chinese nuns the Burmese language as a volunteer.

Aug 2023 - Present Freelancer (coding, testing, consulting)

Upwork

You can go and see my Upwork profile and see what I've done. https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01d717bfa1922910a2

.

Languages

English Fluent

Burmese Fluent

Finnish Beginner

Personal Projects

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023 Blender by using a Python script

I use python to create a terrain object which shows the height

between sea level and ground depending on location.

Skills

Coding Languages

JavaScript, node.js, react, python, C, C++, C#, SQL

Software

Microsoft, Adobe, Docker, UiPath Studio